(Support Admin Watch on kissFlix.co)
Previously on Dating Alys Perez.
Your mom says you're going on a vacation?
Drake?!
This place is a perfect place.
To relax, enjoy...
and be in love!
With the nature, of course.
Would you
treat me the same way you did before?
Sure.
Oh, geez!
What are these for?
This one is for your birthday.
This one is for anniversary.
For monthsary.
For saying thank you.
For saying sorry.
For saying i love you.
I'm so happy
that you are part of my life.
Damn you, Palma.
Yeah.
Damn me.
Hello?
I'm coming.
Business partner.
I need to go see him today.
Oh. Really?
Yes.
I can't postpone this, Alys.
Okay.
Uh, Drake?
Hmm?
If I talk to Tripp,
do you promise to
stay with me in this?
I promise.
Let's go?
Let's go.
Breakfast in bed.
Wow, what are we?
Newly weds?
It's just practice.
Confident.
Of course.
What's all this?
Food.
But why is there so much?
Alys,
I'm not letting you go hungry.
- What?
- Oh god!
Oh my god!
Don't startle me, Alys!
That's all for you.
Are you kidding me?
I never cheated on you.
Damn.
All the memories in this room.
Let's go?
Let’s go.
Alys,
are you dating my cousin?
Hey, Silly!
You and Tripp...
You love me too much, right?
More than too much.
...good together.
But Bestie,
you and Drake,
epic together!
I know you still love Drake.
Do you know how I cried when I
found out about you and Tripp?
So, are you leaving Tripp for Drake?
There’s only one thing I ask of you.
Love me a little more.
The moment Drake comes back,
you'll throw me away!
I chose you.
You chose me?
It was Drake,
and it always will be.
Please let me live my life.
All I want
is a life without you.
A life that isn’t focused around you.
You never loved me the
way I wanted you, Perez.
I have to talk to Tripp.
I need to tell him that
Drake and I are back together.
Don't worry.
I promise you,
go after Drake first.
And if it doesn’t work out,
I'll come running back to you.
Hello, Tripp?
Zy?
Can we talk?
In person.
When?
This afternoon.
Around 5pm.
Alright.
Thanks, Tripp.
Zy?
Hmm?
Stand by your decision, okay?
People are hurting already.
This is enough.
This is the last time.
Yeah.
I'm so sorry, Tripp.
Apologize to me in person, Perez.
I think I deserve that.
I will.
I'm so sorry.
See you later, Tripp.
Oh? Where is he going?
He’s going the wrong way.
Huh? Hospital?
What’s happening?
There’s an emergency?
Room 320?
What did you do, Drake?
What did you do?!
What did you do, Drake?!
You’re crazy, Drake!
Why did you do that?
What have you done?
You and Alys can’t be together anymore.
How is she?
Fier is pregnant.
You can't be with Alys anymore.
Who are you?
Marie
Fier
Sandoval!
Who is Fier?
Don't be jealous.
Don't worry about Fier.
She's nothing compared to you.
I never cheated on you.
It can't be.
It can’t be Drake’s, right?
He couldn’t do that to me.
Hello? Hello, Tripp?
Zy?
Where do we meet up?
I'm almost ready.
Do I really want to drag him into this?
Tripp had already been
through hell because of me.
I don’t want to drag him
into my problems anymore.
Zy?
Are you crying?
Hello?
Are you still there?
Tripp...
Hey.
Why do you sound like that?
I'm sorry.
I’m not feeling well right now.
Can I meet you tomorrow instead?
I'm sorry.
What? But —
Why is he here?
Will he tell me the truth,
or will he just lie to me?
Either way,
it’ll hurt just the same.
-Alys...
-What do you need?
Alys?
What?
I love you.
Is he going to tell me that
I love you but I can't marry you?
Drake, do you want to
tell me something?
Alys,
I know you hate lies.
And I don't like lying.
I hate lies.
I loathe them.
Lies are destructive.
Especially in relationships.
You know that, right?
So, what is it?
Alys...
Fier is pregnant.
Are you the father?
Alys.
Go away, Drake. Leave me alone!
No, wait.
- I said, leave!
- Alys!
Don't you understand?
Alys, you’re the one I love,
not Fier!
You should’ve thought of that
before you got her pregnant!
It's already done, Alys.
I can't escape from this.
All I can do now,
is be a good father to our child.
But, Alys...
you’re the only one I love.
It’s always been you.
You had her pregnant, Drake!
Do you think I’d just let that slide?!
Alys, I'd never ask you to do that.
All I ask
is that you stay with me.
Don't leave me.
You got her pregnant, Drake!
Damn, she was your first!
Do you want to drive me insane?!
- Huh?
- But you're the one I want, Alys.
Only you.
I'm serious, Drake!
Don’t mess with me!
Alys, Fier was a mistake!
I will always choose you.
Get it together, Palma!
I am this close to hitting you!
My head hurts so much
considering the fact that
you're becoming a father,
and you have the nerve
to make a fool out of me.
Alys,
I'm not trying to fool you.
I’ve wanted to marry you for a long time.
How are you so calm about this?!
Can’t you panic at least a little?!
Fuck, Drake.
You’re going to have a baby!
Alys, I’m calm because
you haven’t run away from me yet.
Try leaving me.
You’ll see how panicked I’ll get.
God, how am I supposed to do this?
I love Drake. I really do.
I can accept that he has a child
with someone else. But…
But I'm not sure if my conscience
can take ruining that child's life.
Hey! Are you okay?
Just go see her already.
Who?
Don't act dense. You're like...
Whatever.
It’s obvious you can’t be still
because you’re worried.
Worried?
You're making things up.
Worried about who?
Come on, man.
Deny all you want.
We both know the truth.
You can't fool me.
She said she wasn't feeling well.
She says she can’t do it today.
She wants to meet me tomorrow instead.
Well, there you go.
It’s already set.
But, of course, there's
nothing you can do about it.
You need to give her
the space she needs, right?
It’s not as easy as it sounds.
You know,
you're confusing me.
You know what we should do?
Let's go out!
But you're paying, of course.
I haven't been treated by
Marco Palma in a while.
Stop it.
I've got something else to do.
Do whatever you want.
There you go again.
You keep yourself busy,
because you’re not with Alys anymore.
So you can forget about her.
Whatever.
You'll move on one day, Marco Palma.
Alys.
Drake, how could you do this?
You're having a child with Fier.
You should be with her.
I don't want to marry her.
I'm sure about that.
I don't want to marry Fier
just because she's having my child.
I want to marry the
person that I love.
That is you, Alys.
Drake, I love you too, but...
I want to talk to Fier if I can.
Alys, I'm telling you —
Drake, please.
I feel like I'll go crazy
if I don't talk to her.
Alys, you’ll only drive yourself
crazier if you talk to her.
So forget about it.
Drake, please. Let me talk to Fier.
I'm begging you.
Okay. Tomorrow.
We still have each
other despite everything.
We can get through this. I know it.
This is just but a
little wave in our boat.
It won't sink our ship down.
Go home.
I'm going to rest.
I won't go home until
I know you're okay.
I'm okay. Now, go home.
You're not okay. I know you.
I'm okay. I promise.
Drake, it’s not like the heaviness
I’m feeling will just go away.
But I'll try.
For the both of us.
Go home.
Drake! What a surprise!
What are you doing here?
I just came to see Alys.
Perfect.
I just brought some food from Botejyu.
I heard you love ramen.
So, let's eat.
I'm sorry, Mom.
But Drake was about to go home.
Okay, maybe next time.
Yes, Auntie.
I'll go ahead.
Uncle, Auntie. Alys.
Alys...
Are you getting back together?
Mommy...
Come on! Spill the tea.
Mommy, please. Not right now.
Maybe next time.
Are you like that with your mom now?
Hon...
I know you're happy.
Let's leave them be.
Okay, fine.
Aren’t you going to walk him out?
I was supposed to but you stopped me.
Okay. Go ahead.
Let's eat.
You go ahead.
I'll get something first.
What happened here?
Go home.
What about your mom?
This is better.
It's best to keep things
between us for now.
I don’t know how I’ll react
if the topic of Fier comes up again.
There's too much
going on in my head and
honestly, there's no room
for anyone else's opinions.
Is that okay with you?
We'll talk tomorrow, Drake.
Okay?
Okay.
Alys...
Only you can make me marry you.
1131.
Always.
You know me too well, Drake Palma.
Shit!
I forgot to turn on my phone.
My god.
I hope I didn't miss anything.
Hey, Perez!
Are we still going to meet today?
Hello?
Are you okay?
Zyril, please answer!
Need to reschedule.
Sorry. Will let you know when.
I'm so sorry, Tripp.
I really can't risk talking
to you in my state like this.
My head is all over the place.
There’s just too much going on.
You can do this, Alys.
Let's get this over and done with.
I feel like my chest is about to burst.
I want to fight for this.
But if Fier uses her baby against me,
I might give up before
she finishes talking.
She's having a baby with Drake.
What chance do I have against that?
Noob.
Look at me.
Hmm?
Now, look at you.
Why aren't you nervous?
Because I’m going to face this
with you by my side.
Palma...
Fier really is pregnant with your child.
Otherwise, if this is
one of your tricks again,
God knows what I'll do to you.
If this is one of his messed up tricks,
god, I'll kill him.
Alys,
I don’t want to risk
what we have now, okay?
I was just thinking about this last night.
We'd come here
to settle things but...
It's harder than I thought.
Alys...
If this is hard for you,
then you don't have to do this.
But this is for the best, Drake.
And you know it.
So you really want to talk to her?
I need to talk to Fier.
For my sanity!
After you talk to her,
if you ask me again,
I'll only have one answer.
You're the one I want to marry, Alys.
Okay, but not now.
Let's go?
Let’s go.
Game?
Game.
Who are you?
Don't be so nosy, Lourd.
Leave us.
What do you need?
Fier, I just...
I just wanna talk.
What else do you want?
Fier...
Is Drake really the father of your child?
It just seems so hard to believe.
Honestly...
I still don't wanna believe it.
It's my body, Alys.
Surely,
I'd know who the
father of my child is.
Right?
And you?
Hardcore loser.
What are you doing here?
Don't call me a loser.
So what do you prefer?
Douche?
Jerk?
No.
I still prefer loser.
It suits you.
You freaking banged me
and you’re going to tell me
you don’t want to take responsibility?
Wait, what?
My parents put me through school,
not so you could get me pregnant
and then run away.
To hell with you, Palma!
Fier, I won’t run away from you.
So walking out wasn't
considered running?
You fucking moron!
Drake, I'm not like what other
people might actually think.
I'm educated.
You don't get to treat me like trash.
This is what I’ve been thinking about.
I was afraid this would happen.
I'm also a woman.
I know how hard it is for Fier.
I couldn't even begin to imagine
what I'd do if I were in her place.
Begging someone to marry you wasn't exactly
something anyone would want to do.
It's pathetic and degrading.
I only begged once.
And you rejected me.
Who do you think you are?
Who are you for me to beg?
You're just some guy I slept with.
Unfortunately,
you gave me a souvenir.
I can't take what I'm hearing
from them anymore.
It’s too much to hear,
much more to handle.
I’ll need to leave.
No!
You listen, Alys!
I'm gonna have this child.
And you're gonna have to suck it up!
I was Drake's first.
And I'm the mother of his child.
Marry him.
Get his fucking last name.
But you can’t take away what I have.
You will never outwin me, Perez.
Remember that!
Don't think about it.
Easier said than done, Drake.
It’s hard not to be affected
by the things I’ve heard.
You can say all you want.
Not to think about it or
let it get to me.
But deep down, I know.
That Fier is telling the truth.
She has something I will never have.
I told you.
There’s no good outcome
from talking to her.
What do you want me to do?
Act blind or deaf?
If I didn't talk to her,
it would be on my conscience all my life.
Do you have any better ideas, Drake?
I don't know.
All I know is I don't want
you to stress over this, Alys.
How could I not be stressed, Drake?
My boyfriend is having a
baby with somebody else.
And she wants you to stay with her.
If that's not problematic enough,
maybe I have no idea
what a real problem is.
I can't take this, Drake.
And I don't want to lie to you, Drake.
I know this problem will only get harder,
and it will be impossible to resolve
and there's just way
too many people involved.
Just stop.
How?
I love you enough to know that
we'll get through everything, Alys.
You always know exactly what to say.
Just don't leave me, Alys.
I won't leave you, Drake.
I'm not running away.
Why do you always
think that I'll leave you?
I don’t know.
I guess I’m just being paranoid.
Why?
Because I love you so much, Alys.
And think this isn’t healthy anymore.
And I don't even know what
I can do about it.
But I love you so much, Alys.
The mere thought that
you'd leave me again,
it’s already killing me.
Drake,
look at me.
I'm not leaving you.
I won't go away.
So don't be scared.
Okay?
I hope so.
Okay.
I’m going.
The thought of forgetting you, Alys,
is already driving me insane.
Can you feel that?
That's the heart of a man
who is obsessed with you.
You always call me selfish.
But Alys, is that really selfish?
To put your well being first
before my own feelings?
I'm still in love with you, Alys.
Always.
Marry me or lose me forever.
Drake, will you marry me?
I know this is the worst plan of them all.
But...
I've always wanted to marry you, Drake.
And I know this is nowhere
near the perfect timing but...
I just can't help myself.
My heart keeps on telling me this.
Drake Sebastian Jimenez Palma...
I know I rejected you to the
point that I've lost count already.
And I know this is the wrong decision.
Considering the fact that you're
having a child and...
I know it's unfair for the baby.
And for Fier, but...
I love you so much, Drake.
And...
I know myself.
I know that
when all of this gets
too much to bear for me,
I'm gonna give up.
I don't want to give up on you, Drake.
I don't want —
I don't want to give you up again.
Fuck, I gave you up way too many times.
So please,
just this once,
can I please be selfish?
Will you please marry
this selfish girl, Drake?
Drake, you're scaring me!
Drake!
Don't you want to marry me?
Are you marrying Fier
because of the baby?
If that's the case, please tell me.
Please.
Say something, anything!
Please!
Say anything!
Are you going crazy, Alys?
I will marry you in a heartbeat.
Wherever, whenever.
Why aren’t you answering me?!
Are you trying to
make me worry to death?
I can't even feel my face.
Damn, Perez.
I love you so much.
Mom...
Mom, Dad,
I have something to say.
Drake and I...
We're getting married.
I'm sorry, Alys. But you can't.
Drake,
we're at the hospital.
Please come.
Fier needs you.
Hello, Tripp?
Why do I feel that
something is wrong?
I feel like something bad
is gonna happen.
Please.
I hope it's nothing.
No, I'm just overthinking.
I just got her back.
I don't want to lose her again.
On the next episode of
Dating Alys Perez.
Come on, Mom!
Dad accepted you even when
you had a child that wasn't his.
Why —
Alys, I'm sorry.
Tripp...
I'll go to you.
I promised I'd never leave you, right?
Shut up, Fier!
I didn't raise you just to
be pregnant and unwed!
But Dad...
Maybe that’s just how it is.
Some dreams change as we grow older.
Some are replaced.
There’s only thing that hasn’t
been replaced.
What?
I think the question should be...
Who?
Actually, I don’t know if
any of this is right anymore.
I also don’t know, Alys.
All I know is that I love you so much.